Eli Brewer

720-375-2131 • Cabot, AR • Enso@enso.codes

SUMMARY

User Experience Generalist with 3 years of experience in Digital Design and Front-End Web Development working with HTML5, SCSS, and JQuery to deliver exceptional user experiences to the web. Proficient at leading and contributing to highly collaborative work environments, managing multiple projects in Agile frameworks, and designing, developing, and testing mobile friendly websites.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Document Controller

Jan. 2022 - Present

Allen Flores Consulting Group | Searcy, AR

- Maintain and update policies, procedures and state guidelines in clinical forms, manuals, and reduction programs using Microsoft Word and Adobe Acrobat.
- Creation of PDF documents, scheduling, and posting content online; maintain company website and training posts.
- Experience with working with WordPress content management system (CMS) and Vimeo.
- Ability to create, modify, and optimize web page graphics.

Freelance Web Designer

Mar 2021 - Present

Enso.codes | Cabot, AR

- Coordinated with clients to finalize designs and confirm requirements of project scope.
- Consistently meet deadlines and requirements for all projects.
- Researched and evaluated market pricing for web hosting and recommended the most efficient and cost-effective solutions to prospective and active clients.
- Managed projects through Trello and Planyway to track status reports, managing checklists, and logging work time. Client and guest access to Trello made available upon approved project charter agreement.

Web/Graphic Design Intern

Aug. 2021 - Oct. 2021

Arkansas Center for Data Sciences | Little Rock, AR

- Web based learning IT Consulting Intern working with JIRA and Confluence in Agile development processes with Inspiring Innovative Concepts, LLC.
- Worked closely with other Design Interns and Project Manager in a dynamic remote team environment, observing both detailed specifications and immediate word-of-mouth change requests. Used Illustrator and Adobe XD for designing print samples and website mock-ups.

PROJECTS

Web Designer

Dec. 2021 - Jan. 2022

ZEROSEV | Miami, FL

- Web design project for Brian Alvarado at ZEROSEV.com
- Created wireframes in Adobe XD. Managed project through use of Trello and Planyway for tracking status reports and implementation alongside client access.

Front-End Web Developer

Mar. 2021 - May 2022

Arripe Gladium | Online

- Worked alongside 25 creators on Season of the Plague (SOTP) inspired by Bungie's Destiny 2.
- Reported routine website progression to former Project Director during SOTP development.
- Created low-fidelity mock-up for conceptual "Season of Content" using FIGMA. Front-end Coding Development with HTML5, SCSS, and JavaScript for count
- Organized and tracked website progress using Trello.
- Tracked site SEO and traffic through Google Analytics. Conducted user experience surveys to gain
 more insight to usability of the website on mobile, tablet, and desktop including resolutions exceeding
 2K.

EDUCATION

Web Design & Development - Bachelor of Arts | University of Arkansas at Little Rock

General Studies - Associate of Arts | Tarrant County College District

2016-2020

High School Diploma | Cabot High School, Cabot, AR

2010-2011

GPA: 3.4/4.0

COURSES & TRAININGS

Google Professional UX Certification | Arkansas Center for Data Sciences

Est. Dec 2022

SKILLS

Key Skills: Web Development & Maintenance, Website Testing, Website Troubleshooting, Prototyping, Wireframing, Problem-solving, Consulting, Project Management

Technical Skills: CSS, CSS3, SASS, HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery, Photoshop, Illustrator, Adobe XD, Figma, WordPress, DreamWeaver, Visual Studio Code, Illustrator, JIRA, Confluence, Trello, Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Google Suite